Guide to the Medical Center records, 1825-2005 RG0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Personnel files, circa 1970-circa 1989; RG0007 Series 1; 34.5 Linear feet
  - Jacobson, Cecil B., undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jaffee, I. Sidney, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Department:Ent. Un-pt
  - Jakoby, Ruth E., undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Jenkins, Roger T., undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Department:P.S.
  - Jenkins, Ramon B., undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Jeste, Dilip V., undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Department: Ne Urolo
  - Jeyaraj, Francis, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, David C., undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Johnson, Rodney A., undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Steele R., undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Jones, Thomas I., undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Jones, Vann K., undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
    Department:Clinical Inst/Med
  - Joseph, William Gen., undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Joslyn, Kenneth E., undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Department:Asst prof health care/Med
  - Jung, May T., undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Kalman, Joel P., undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Kanal, Nirmal, undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    Department:Ophthar
  - Karim, Najmaldin, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    Department: Ne Urol.Surg
  - Kark, John A., undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Karl, Norman J., undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Karpick, Ronald J., undated (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Department:Pulmonary D./Med
  - Kasper, Thomas E., undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Kass, Evan J., undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Katz, Auriella, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    Department: Surg/Dent
  - Katz, Lawrence A., undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Katz, Stephen, undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Katzen, Barry T., undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Katzen, Harvey I., undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Kaufman, Michael A., undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Kaufman, Ronald P., undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Katzberg, Richard, undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Kaveggia, Laszio, undated (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Kehoe, James, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
    Department: Med.
  - Kelly, Aileen, undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Kesling, Robert, undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Kelly, John F., undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
    Department: Ped.
  - Kent, Georgia, undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Kessner, David M., undated (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Kim-Chul, undated (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Kimball, Christina E., undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - King, Terry, undated (Box 23, Folder 49)
    Department: Surg/Vascular
  - King, Lucy J., undated (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Kloko, Gideon M., undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Kirby, Edward C., undated (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Kirby, Smith Hayden, undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Kirchner, Francis, undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Kirchner, Peter T., undated (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Kirkland Jr.,Leland R., undated (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Kirkwcxxi, John R., undated (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Kirmani, Nigar, undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Kirson, Stanley M., undated (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Klaus, Hanna, undated (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Kleinman, Bradford A., undated (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Klingermaier, Charles H., undated (Box 23, Folder 62)
    Department: Anest
  - Klirsfeld, Dava L., undated (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Klug Panpit P., undated (Box 23, Folder 64)
    Department:Asst. prof. Med
  - Kneller, Martin S., undated (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Knerr, Robert J., undated (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Knudson, Delmar H., undated (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Kogan, Leonard L., undated (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Kolvereid, Edward R., undated (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Koos, Wolfgang T., undated (Box 23, Folder 70)
    Department:Assoc.Clincal prof/Neur Surg
  - Korengold, George Me., undated (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Koulouris, Spiridon, undated (Box 23, Folder 72)
    Department:Clin. Instr/Neur/Department: Surg
  - Kovarick, Susan, undated (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Kraftowitz, Robert, undated (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Kramer, Celia A., undated (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Kramer, Norman C., undated (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Kramer, Peter D., undated (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Kramer, Robert, undated (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Kransnow, Steven H., undated (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Kratz, Rudiger, undated (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Kreuz, Leo E., undated (Box 23, Folder 81)
    Department: Psych and Beh. Sci
  - Krinn, Malvin D., undated (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Krogh, Paul H., undated (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Kross, Timothy J., undated (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Krufky, Edward L., undated (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Kullick, Margarita, undated (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Kurzbard, Stephen J., undated (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - Kushner, Edward, undated (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Kushner, Jack, undated (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Laby-Gotthem, Shelley L., undated (Box 23, Folder 90)
    Department:Int. Department: Med
  - Lai-Alfred S., undated (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Lai-Patrick, undated (Box 23, Folder 92)
    Department: Med Research
  - Lachman, Sander E., undated (Box 23, Folder 93)
    Department: Ped Ctsy
- Medical staff office files, 1969-1989; RG0007 Series 2; 12 Linear feet
  This series consists of minutes, correspondence, by-laws, committee and department files. The materials range in date from 1969-89.
  - PEC Minutes, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - PEC Correspondence, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - PEC Business office, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - PEC Administrators Report: Late change, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - PEC HMO, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - PEC Communications, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - PEC: List of members, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - PEC minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - PEC correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - PEC Legal matters, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - PEC correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - PEC: Minutes and list of members, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - PEC correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - PEC: Bad Debts minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - PEC Business office newsletters, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - PEC Billing system, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - PEC Computer downtime, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - PEC credit cards, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - PEC status reports, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - PEC correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - PEC agendas, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - PEC: minutes and list of members, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - PEC business office newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Business office reports, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Computer downtime, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bad Debts minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - PEC correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - PEC minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - PEC special reports and analyses, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - PEC HMO, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - PEC, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    The original finding aid put a question mark after the title
  - PEC, 19721973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - PEC, 19711972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - PEC: minutes and committee members, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - PEC correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - PEC special reports, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - PEC HMO, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - PEC AGPA, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - PEC correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - PEC agendas, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - PEC: minutes and list of members, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - PEC Bad Debt subcommittee minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - PEC business office newsletters, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - PEC business office reports, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - PEC: minutes and committee members, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - PEC correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - PEC agendas, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - PEC business office reports, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - PEC Bad Debt subcommittee, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - PEC Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - PEC, 07/09/1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - PEC, 08/14/1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - PEC, 09/11/1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - PEC, 10/18/1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - PEC, 12/13/1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - PEC, 01/10/1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - PEC, 02/14/1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - PEC, 03/14/1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - PEC, 04/11/1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - PEC, 05/09/1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - PEC, 06/13/1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - PEC: minutes and committee members, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - PEC correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - PEC agendas, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - PEC business office reports, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Accounts Review Committee on Physician rotation, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - B & FC: minutes and list of members, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Special reports, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - By-laws, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Procedures, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Members and list of minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Fiscal reports, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - B & FC Members, and Executive Committee minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Executive Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Agendas, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Administrators reports, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - MFA proposed contract change balloting, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Committee members, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Agendas, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Minutes and list of members, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Agendas, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Minutes and list of members, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Agenda, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Membership members, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Executive Committee agendas, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Minutes and list of members, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Executive Committee correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Patient visit statistics, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Quarterly reports, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Monthly reports, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dermatology, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Medicine, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Neurology, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Neuro-surgery, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Opthamology, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Orthopedics, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Psychiatry, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Radiology, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Surgery, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Urology, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Quarterly reports, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Monthly reports, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dermatology, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Medicine, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Neurology, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Neurosurgery, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Opthamology, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Orthopedics, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Psychiatry, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Surgery, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Urology, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Laboratory, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Radiology, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dermatology, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Medicine, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Neurology, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Neurosurgery, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Opthamology, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Orthopedic surgery, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Psychiatry, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Surgery, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Urology, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Radiology, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Laboratory, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Dermatology, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Medicine, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Neurology, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Neurosurgery, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Opthamology, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Orthopedic surgery, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Psychiatry, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Surgery, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Urology, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Radiology, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Laboratory, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Dermatology, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Medicine, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Neurology, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Neurosurgery, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Opthamology, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Orthopedic surgery, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Psychiatry, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Surgery, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Urology, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Radiology, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Lab medicine, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Patient visit statistics, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Medicine, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Neurology, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Opthamology, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Orthopedic surgery, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Neurosurgery, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Dermatology, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Psychiatry, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Surgery, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Urology, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Laboratory, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Radiology, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence, 07/1984 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence, 08/1984 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence, 09/1984 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence, 10/1984 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence, 11/1984 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence, 12/1984 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence, 01/1985 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence, 02/1985 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence, 03/1985 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence, 04/1985 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence, 06/1985 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - MFA patient statistics, 07/1984-06/1985 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Executive Committee, By-laws of the clinic, procedures of the clinic, and list of members, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stats, attendance, agendas, correspondence, clinic executive committee minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Surgical case review committee, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ad hoc committees of the clinic on ACD salaries, minutes, correspondence, and reports, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ad hoc committees of the clinic minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ad hoc committees of Executive Committee, Advisory Committee, Long Range Planning Committee, and Space Committee, 19721974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ad hoc committees of clinic committee on clinic goals, committy on policy regarding sabbatical, annual, and sick leave, committee on public affairs and public relations, and committee on student health affairs, 19691972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Nominating committee, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Patient service operations manual, 19691972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Faculty practice committee members, minutes, correspondence, agendas, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Faculty practice committee, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Meetings on July 20, September 14, October 19, and December 14
  - Faculty practice committee, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Meetings on January 18, February 22, March 19, May 17, and June 21
  - Faculty practice committee correspondence, agendas, minutes, and attachments, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Medicine, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Emergency request, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Dermatology, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Medicine, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Opthamology, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Psychiatry, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Surgery, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Urology, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Capital Equipment Committee: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clinical audit committee: reports and minutes, 07/1971-06/1972 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Clinical audit committee: Correspondence, 07/1972-06/1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Clinical audit committee: Correspondence, 07/1973-06/1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Clinical audit committee: Minutes, 07/1974-06/1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Clinical audit committee: Correspondence, 07/1974-06/1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Clinical audit committee: Statistics, 07/1975-06/1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Clinical audit committee: Fiscal reports, 07/1975-06/1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Clinical audit committee: Correspondence, 07/1975-06/1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Clinical audit committee: Minutes and members, 07/1975-06/1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Clinical audit committee: Statistics, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Clinical audit committee: Correspondence, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Clinical audit committee: List of members, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Space committee: Correspondence, 07/1983-06/1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Space committee: Correspondence, 04/10/1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Space committee: Correspondence, 06/25/1984 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Space committee: Space requests, 07/1986-06/1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Space committee: Correspondence, 07/1986-06/1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Capital equipment committee: List of members and minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Capital equipment committee: Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Capital equipment committee: List of members and minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Capital equipment committee: Announcements, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Capital equipment committee: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Capital equipment committee: List of members and minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Capital equipment committee: Announcements, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Capital equipment committee: Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Capital equipment committee: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Capital equipment committee: Expenditures, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Capital equipment committee: MFA agenda, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Capital equipment committee: MFA minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Capital equipment committee: Emergency, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Capital equipment committee: Routine requests, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Capital equipment committee: Routine requests, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Capital equipment committee: Medicine, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Capital equipment committee: Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Capital equipment committee: Surgery, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Capital equipment committee: Radiology, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Capital equipment committee: Emergency requests, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Capital equipment committee: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Capital equipment committee: Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Capital equipment committee: General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Capital equipment committee: Emergency requests, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Capital equipment committee: Surgery, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Capital equipment committee: Ortho-surgery, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Capital equipment committee: Urology, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Capital equipment committee: Psychiatry, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Capital equipment committee: MFA cashiers, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Capital equipment committee: Office of the medical director, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Capital equipment committee: Dermatology, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Budget and Finance Committee: Correspondence and special reports, 07/1977-06/1978 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Budget and Finance Committee: Members, minutes, and correpsondence, 07/1978-06/1979 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Accreditation Committee: Reports and miscellaneous information, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Accreditation Committee: Members, minutes, correspondence, and survey documents, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Accreditation Committee: Members, minutes, and correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Accreditation Committee: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Accreditation Committee: Correspondence and minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Audit Committee: Members, minutes, correspondence, and fiscal reports, 07/1980-06/1981 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Audit Committee: Members, minutes, correspondence, and fiscal reports, 07/1981-06/1982 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Audit Committee: Members, minutes, correspondence, and fiscal reports, 07/1982-06/1983 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Audit Committee: Members, minutes, correspondence, and agendas, 07/1983-06/1984 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Faculty practice committee: Correspondence, agendas, and minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Faculty practice committee: Questionnaire and subcommittee, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Faculty practice committee: Agendas, minutes, and correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Faculty practice committee: List of members, minutes, correspondence, and subcommittee, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Plant operations, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Includes neurology, dermatology, urology, medicine, and psychiatry
  - Plant operations, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Includes orthopedics, opthamology, radiology, burns lobby, neuro-surgery, correspondence
  - Burns Building work requests, 12/1985-12/1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - By-laws and procedures, 07/1970-06/1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Clinic by-laws and procedures, 07/1971-06/1972 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - By-laws and procedures: ACD by-laws review, 07/1973-06/1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Original finding aid does not explain abbreviation
  - By-laws and procedures, 07/1972-06/1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)